it’s not me but in your report the
это же не я а б с е вашем отчете
east direction so you
восточное направление так пойдешь
will go agree with the east direction as the east
согласитесь с восточного направления как
does not turn according to the compass in the
не поворачивается по компасу восток на
east at least apples and the country, then
востоке как минимум яблок и стране то
something if we are wrong, I think that
что нибудь если мы не правы я думаю что
this country will not be able to exist
эта страна не сможет существовать
as well as from such
как и из такой
if we are wrong with such pride
если мы не правы с такой гордостью
hello friends on your devil people
здрасте друзей на твои дьявол людей
depended I ask how you feel about the
зависели спрашиваю как вы относитесь к
war in ukraine
войне в украине
hi the war in ukraine is bad, that is, you
привет войне в украине плохо то есть вы
think that your
считаете что не правильно сделано ваше
state
государство что давило выискал украина
did not do it right, what pressed ukraine found out not this is right
не этого это правильно
capachini
capachini
well, so that it doesn’t happen  war the mouse is bad with
ну чтобы не было войны мышка плохо
politics, I don’t understand that, that is, you
политикой не я так понял то есть вы
treat it badly, so you will
плохо относитесь к ней поэтому вы
support the troops of your country in our
поддержите вот войск вашей страны в нашу
country so that there is no war,
страну чтобы не было войны а
why is it necessary what kind of war
почему это нужно какая бы война
happens because you didn’t lead your troops from Lucy happened  she walked which one,
войска от люси случилось она шла какая
which one is higher there themselves all war war
как какая выше там сами все война война
war war don’t don’t look to
война война не не смотрите подучить вот
learn your troops invaded the territory of
в ваши войска вторглись на территорию
ukraine so as not to  there was a war
украины чтобы не было войны
so that there was no war, then it
чтобы не было войны то
turns out that you started a war so that there was
получается вы начали войну чтобы не было
no war, no, they came to stop you to end the
нет пришли прекратить вам прекратить
war, then yes, and how you find it, you
войну то да и как вы обретете вывели
understand who we fought with America
понял а с кем мы там с америкой воевали
with Belarusians with Moldova
с белорусами с молдовой
fought with Russians who lived on the
воевали с русскими которые проживали на
territory of
территории
Ukraine
украины
seriously  and with some Russians, well, they fought there
серьезно а с какими-то русскими ну там
themselves to create a world Marat in the Donbass can’t
сами создать мир не может марат на
meadows why the Russians lived there you couldn’t
донбассе луга че там жили русские вы не
kill you with them water like a menu
смогли убивали вы с ними воде как меню
how did we
как мы их вали
defend them you plucked here or just
защите вы срывали вот или только что
opened reports without me every day
открывала отчеты без я каждый день
every  day .
каждый день .
once again, let’s and the judge understand for himself, it
еще раз давайте и судья для себя понял
turns out Ukraine so
получается украина так
decided let’s kill Russians in the
решила давайте мы поубиваем русских на
Donbass and
донбассе так и
start killing yes,
начала убивать да а
why,
почему
probably, you didn’t want them to live well there,
вероятно вы не хотели чтобы они там жили
and why in Kharkov, for example,
хорошо а почему в харькове например вот
Kharkov, there are also a lot of Russian-speaking
харькове тоже очень много русскоязычных
people there even  Russians, maybe why
людей там даже русских может почему
Ukraine didn’t kill Russians in Kharkov,
украина не убивала русских в харькове
killing not, but I don’t say travolta speaking
убивая не а я не говорю траволта язычную
Russia, that’s about Russians, why
руси вот про русских почему ручки в
Ukraine didn’t kill pens in Kharkov, but because
харькове украина не убивала а потому что
it was in Donetsk that Russians and Luhansk region
именно в донецке и русские и луганщине
became against the authorities that the authorities in
стали против при власти которые власть в
Ukraine, the authorities to charge his power
украине власти заряжать его власть
it’s hard for you to come here to the authorities who seized
ты сюда сложно власти которая захватила
power at that time to say maidan well
власть то время говорить майдан хорошо
let’s
давайте
take the story in 2014 so
возьмем так историю в 2014 году так с
how did the hostilities begin in
чего начались военные действия в
ukraine well in the Donetsk region
украине ну в донецкой области
people who are a
люди которые
tribute from the Donetsk region to Donetsk and
дань из донецкой области донецке и
Luhansk
луганске
they stood up against
они встали против
them look here you say what
они смотрите вот вы говорите что
started  in hostilities, from what
началась в военных действий вот с какого
day hostilities began in the
дня начались военные действия в
fourteenth year  we arrived,
четырнадцатом году мы приехали ваши
so people
значит люди
had to the central part of Western
имели до центральной части западной
culture and began to kill on what
культуры и начали убивать в какой вот
date can you see the first murder of Russians
дату можете вот первое убийство русских
when it
когда прошло
happened let's here we are now with this video I won't just write not when when the first murders of Russians began in the Donbass let's google it
донбассе давайте погуглите
not very  interesting, but
не очень интересно а
you yourself are not google or, as I understand it, not not
вы сами не google или так понимаю не не
google, he
google он
may have the right not to be interested, so
может быть имеет право не интересно так
you press some date and then I will tell you
какую-то дату вы нажмете а я потом скажу
how the war started,
с чего началась война
that is, you haven’t tried just
то есть вы не пробовали вот именно такую
this one, take it, I just know that the war is from
вот возьмите я просто знаю что война от
It began with the fact that on April 12,
началась с того что 12 апреля тысячу
2014, a thousand Russian militants from Russia,
2014 года так русские боевики из россии
so under the command of
так под командованием
special forces there, from the tower of
спецназовцы там вашего там с башни
yours, somehow Girkin shooters, entered the
как-то стрелков-гиркин а вошли в
Ukrainian city of Slavyansk ok Slavyansk
украинский город славянск ок славянск
france and seized the police station and
france и захватили отделение полиции и
installed their kind of proxy there
установили там свою как бы вот прокси
they began to introduce such power as
власть такую так начали вводили как
victims, but they captured and fled, they
жертвами но захватили и смылись
captured the police station, they were with
захватили отделение полиции они с
grenades at the level with grenade launchers along  in the summer,
гранатами уровне с гранатометами подлете
that is, a military seizure and people from another
то есть военный захват и люди из другой
country from Russia come and
страны из россии приходят и в украине
seize a police station in Ukraine,
захватывают отделение полиции а
and two days later it began in the actual
через два дня началась в собственно от
terrorist operation,
террористической операции да
yes, I told you dash cam there were Russian
вот я вам сказал dash cam были русские
troops, also google it in a whisper, you
войска также его шепотом гуглите вы уже
will be on google for a long time and  when, after all, the
долго будете на google и когда все таки
first Russian was killed by evil ukry from
первого русского убили злые из
central and western ukraine,
центральной и западной украины
well, only yes, they googled where
ну только да вот нагуглили куда когда-то
everyone once started that you don’t rush you
все начали что у не торопите вы столько
have been gathering thoughts here for so long how many
времени тут собирались мыслями сколько
years is not such advice to me, I just thought you were
лет не такой совет мне просто я думал вы
already there on google and  who is there google
уже там на google и у кого там google
weak some kind of
слабенький какой-то
index
индекс
it is weaker than pretty jersey
он слабее довольно фуфайки
google and faster can find
google и быстрее может найти
american one you can’t
американский нельзя
wear it uncomfortable for nails
носим неудобный для ногтей
it will help in this youtube better in the same place it
он поможет в этом ютюбе лучше там же
seems like it’s Bashinsky yes you’re
вроде как это башинский да вы времени
tattoo time tell me he became when
тату скажите вот я он стал когда
you started them here from  why did they
началась вы им здесь из чего они
start,
начались
are you talking about the fact that Russian Russians entered there,
это вы говорите о том что там зашли
whether Russians and Russians and
русское русские ли русские да русские и
the citizens of Russia and the fault of the citizens of the
на граждане россии да и вина граждан
citizens  Russia, yes, it was inappropriate for me to recruit
граждане россии да ко мне было неуместно
locals later and that
местных набирали потом и что
we were attacked
нам нападали
by methods, see even
методами смотрите вот даже гиркин
Girkin shooters, then where he said that his
стрелков то куда он сказал что заход его
group had entered Slavyansk and started this war before
группу славянск и начал эту войну до
that, in general, everything was calm and peaceful,
этого вообще все спокойно и мирно было
they went in and did and militants began to
они зашли так и сделали и начали
gather from  Russian
съезжаться боевики с россии кадровые
military personnel also, and then you look
военные также и тогда вот вы смотрите вы
from which part of Russia you yourself
из какого из какой части россии сами
require data to Moscow, yes, you are there
данными требует к москве да вот вы там и
and for some reason I land people somewhere from
вот я почему-то сушу люди где-то из
Moscow and Siberia, and there and so they
москвы и ских то сибири и там и так они
know more about  what is happening in
больше знают про то что происходит в
ukraine
украине
than what is happening in russia and you you
чем то что происходит в россии а вы вы
never
никогда не
no
нет
I didn’t talk live here in roulette with the
я не здесь в рулетке вживую общался с
guys from Donetsk from Luhansk and I
ребятами из донецка из луганска а я вот
talked here they are exactly about
здесь общался они вот они вот именно об
this and they say that we were a broker
этом и говорят о том что мы были брокер
it’s dumped near you, the conclusion is probably
это свалили вблизи вы вывод наверное
sitting in moscow in some kind of virtual
сидите в москве в каком-то виртуальном
world getac and you know how many people do
мире getac а знаете сколько людей не вот
n’t you come to ukraine when you
вы в украину с не приезжаете когда вы
were in ukraine
были в украине
ukraine the ebook of the camp
украине the ebook лагеря
what are you here you absolutely don’t  you understand
какой ты вот вы абсолютно не понимаете
what happens here when the
что тут происходит вот когда звонит
golden eagles call no-no-no here he was to come
беркутов не-не-не вот он был приехать
here and but to
сюда и а
feel this atmosphere there are
ощутить вот эту атмосферу есть тут эти
some Bandera people there from western and
там бандеровцы какие-то от западной и
central Ukraine now russia
центральной украины вот сейчас россия
loves to watch food holes look now
смотреть любит еду дырах смотри сейчас
russia bombed kharkov russian-speaking
россия разбомбила харьков русскоязычный
Mariupol is Russian-speaking, so why,
мариуполь русскоязычный так почему
but whoever is
но кто
not your America, they could not live to one,
не америка вашего их к одним не могли бы
they stood there and
дожить они там стояли и сами себя
bombed themselves,
бомбили
they stood, but they were in the city, and
они стояли но они в городе были а где же
where else are they outside the city, why
где они ещё находятся за города ну что
are you laughing and only give birth to the city, protect the
смеетесь и лишь родить город оградить
city and protect  wait wait
город и защищать подождите подождите
wait you are the second world war,
подождите вы вторую мировую войну
for example, when there was a blockade of
например так когда была блокада
Leningrad, so the Soviet troops where they
ленинграда так войска советские где
were in Leningrad, of course, the
находились в ленинграде ну конечно
offensive in Leningrad, yes, well,
наступление в ленинграде да ну так а
why didn’t they come out, we’ll go out purely to the
почему они же не вышли выйдем чисто
evil fascists, so they must
полюшко злым фашистам так они должны
defend the city and they are standing in the city
защищать город и они стоят в городе
doing
делаете
look
смотрите еще раз
again why are you laughing, the
для чего вы что смеетесь приходит
invader comes and says stand where it is
захватчик и говорит встань там где мне
convenient for me so you  kill a
удобно будет так тебя убивать
resident see this in the city in any way
житель смотрите это в городе по-любому
civilians than and rush the city, that
мирные жители чем и претесь город то
is, it turns out you come with a war to
есть получаться вы приходите с войной на
someone else's territory then say oh damn
чужую территорию то и говорите ой блин
we woke up a bunch of civilians because
мы разбудили кучу мирные жители потому
it turns out that the troops were in the
что оказывается что войска войска были в
cities
городах
not challenges and we came and  see how
не вызовы и мы пришли и смотрите сколько
many people have already been killed in Ukraine
сколько уже убито людей в украине
by Russians, both civilians and the military, how
русскими и мирных и военных сколько
many in the Donbass, but look
сколько на донбассе а вот смотрите
how much already, even if you take some
сколько уже если даже брать какие-то там
reports about bass in the Donbass, so how many
отчеты о басе на донбассе так сколько
died over the past year, for example, how many
погибло за прошлый год например сколько
it is very easy to see, but now if
это очень легко посмотреть но вот если
you  look from the river and look at
вы посмотрите от реки и посмотрите на
mariupol which there were 400 thousand
мариуполь который там 400 тысяч
people in mariupol so now
население было в мариуполе так а сейчас
mariupol is all in ruins if
мариуполь весь в руинах если украина как
ukraine bombed donbass for 8 years donetsk
вы говорите 8 лет бомбила донбасс донецк
for some reason is not standing and mariupol in
почему то нет стоит а мариуполь через
two months of the month is already in ruins all
два месяца месяца уже в руинах весь
because if only  you would have flooded there
потому что если бы вы туда попёрли бы
since you flooded February February you I wo
так как вы попёрли феврале феврале вы я
n’t be able to
не смогу
hear you, the
вас вас перестала слышно быть
microphone has moved away somewhere
микрофон где-то отошел
now lu  better again if
сейчас лучше еще раз если
you are not more active,
более активно вас
wait, look, we look like and 8
нет подождите смотрите вот выглядим и 8
in the summer they were killed in the Donbas, that is, it
летом убивали на донбассе то есть
turns out that Russia completely destroyed Mariupol in two months in
получается что россия за два месяца за
two months,
два месяца уничтожила полностью
and Ukraine in eight years somehow
мариуполь а украина за восемь лет как то
I didn’t destroy Donetsk
я не уничтожила донецк
if you used a more
если бы вы использовали более
serious and  they used weapons more actively
серьезное и более активно использовали
what happened now in February, the leg
то что произошло сейчас феврале ногу
happened to be a little earlier they didn’t flow in the
произошло быть чуть раньше не текли в
red, and it turns out that we
красно понимали и ваш получается то мы
didn’t bomb the Donbass, so we didn’t destroy
не бомбили донбасс так мы не уничтожали
Donetsk, so
донецк так
what
какой
frequency that allowed you
периодичностью которая позволяла вам
to let you
позволял вам
talk about the fact that an
говорить о том что идет
anti-terrorist operation was underway, they were
антитеррористическая операция они
genocide and  look again and
геноцид и смотрите еще раз и
it allowed the mission we light to
это позволяло миссию мы светом
be present to allow it and
присутствовать это позволить и смотри
look again you say that 8 years look 8
еще раз вы говорите что 8 лет смотрите 8
years if we look at 12 months
лет это если смотрим по 12 месяцев так
it will be only 80 plus 16 ninety-
это будет только 80 плюс 16 девяносто
six months ninety-six
шесть месяцев девяносто шесть месяцев
months  but for some reason it will become everything runs fine,
так но почему-то он станет все нормально
but in this and Mariupol everything is there  everything in the
бежит а в этом а мариуполь все там все в
market for two months of Russian
рынок за два месяца русской
opposition to the war
противодействие войны
you
вы
when the last one is at least one and
когда последний какой нибудь хоть один а
why is it there daily reports the mission
чё там же он ежедневные отчеты миссию
I still consider dragging the conclusion you
мне еще рассмотрите потащите вывод вы
now want to forget to get sick these are all
сейчас хотите забыла болеть это все
reports here and Alaska look again
отчеты вот и аляски смотрите опять
Donetsk yes no it’s worth it so the brownie is
донецк да нет стоит так домовой есть
Mariupol  wiped off the face of the earth the
мариуполь стерт с лица земли
mission is
миссия всё
to watch
смотреть
at least 30 explosions every day and
не менее 30 взрыва ежедневно и мне
now I have enough conscience to say
сейчас совести хватает говорит о том
that we bombed badly if you bombed
чтобы хреново бомбили мы если бы бомбили
you would level it there
бы вы там сравняли посмотреть вот
look you see if you
смотрите вы если так вы относитесь к
belong to this category russia-nato donatti
такой категории россия-нато донатти
cynical hypocrites with personal
циничные лицемеры с личные лицемерие
hypocrisy look
вот смотрите
who let's do this russia dropped
кто давайте так россия сбрасывала
air bombs on mariupol
авиабомбы на мариуполь
history it is top top top so in
история него есть топ-топ-топ так в
the cqi report there you read it russia
отчете cqi там читаете она-то россия
dropped air bombs on
сбрасывал авиабомбы на мариуполь
mariupol report cqi want reports let's
отчете cqi хочу отчеты давайте россия
russia drop bombs russia dropped air bombs on
россия сбрасывал авиабомбы на мариуполь
mariupol just wait  so
вот подождите вы только что настолько
were
были
identified I
опознаны я
no wait called russia bombed
нет подождите вызвали россия бомбила
mariupol i can only  lean in the
мариуполя я могу только опираться на
kitchen on yours about such words that they are
кухне на вашем о таких слова которые они
biased in any way drag this russia
предвзяты по-любому тащить этот россия
bombed mariupol or not
бомбила мариуполь или нет
aviation bombed the troops that
авиация бомбила войска которые
resist the hell of it that bombed
сопротивляются аду этого которые бомбили
russia bombed mariupol so
россия бомбила мариуполь так
russia could only hit the troops that
россия могла бы бить только войска то
is, it’s like this bomb everything so i’ll throw it off
есть она вот так бомбочку все так я
I’ll just throw an aerial bomb on the troops so I’ll just throw it on the tank
вот на танк скину так
so that what will happen before the
там чтобы что будет до
mission, the searches fixed a massive attack from Mariupol, an
миссии обыски фиксировал от мариуполя
example of
массовую атаку примере ракетных систем
multiple launch rocket systems, what conclusion is the fatal year,
залпового огня какой вывод роковой год
and what kind of general
да то какая вообще
I’ll say close close what mission
я скажу закройте закройте какая миссия
would the session with no one allow Russia
бы сессия с никого не допускает россии
to go there  and there it turns out KAMAZ look
туда и там и получается камазе смотрите
how we bombed and pray the dust in the fifteenth
как мы бомбили и молю пыль в пятнадцатом
year if it was ours it turns out
году если он был наш этого получается
your troops bombed the gardener these
ваши войска бомбили садовод эти
terrorists
террористы
who in the fifteenth year and the creed
кто в пятнадцатом году и кредо
controlled a mile by now let's see
контролировала милю по сейчас посмотрим
what their calculations
то их подсчётам
[music]
[музыка]
ask me I wonder what the report is
задавать мне интересно что отчете
well  it’s really real, what’s in the
ну вот реально реально да что там в
report on who bombed Mariupol at
отчете о б с е кто бомбил мариуполь в
fifteen  m year, with multiple launch rocket
пятнадцатом году системами залпового
systems, read onchon, it starts to be
вот дочитайте ончон начинает них
interesting that in this report who then
интересно что в этом отчете кто тогда
bombed the sea share in the fifteenth year,
бомбил морю пай в пятнадцатом году
you will see there they write
увидишь там они пишут
observed nights, volleys are heard from the
наблюдались ночи слышны залпы с
eastern direction of
восточного направления
14 Ukrainian troops, then erase the mission
14 украинских войск то сотрите миссию
or smoky try the eastern
или дымного попробовать восточного
direction, only a few hundred,
направления всего нескольких сотнях все
whatever  sort of all the marks, I still
какому роду все меток я вот все-таки
understand that you are now reading who
понимаю что вы сейчас прочитаете кто же
bombed by ear heard everyone was
бомбили на слух услышал все были
full of joy sent pants
полные штаны радости направили потому
because you confirmed it was not me that it
что вы вы подтвердили не я что
turns out that Mariupol in the 15th year was
получается мариуполь в 15-м году
fired at by your Russian terrorists
обстреливали до ваши русские террористы
from the east, that's all  your
с восточного направления это всё ваша
machete is the east direction how
мачете восточное направление как
to overlay from the east direction how
обложить из восточного направления как
not to turn east according to the compass here are
не поворачивайся по компасу восток вот
the points on you and
на вас точки и
how it doesn’t turn otherwise and
как не поворачивается в остальном и
doesn’t go
не идет
so
вот бы
I wish I could
я сники
do it yes indeed Zakharchenko
сделать да действительно захарченко
noted that he gave the order to open
отметил что он отдавал приказ открыть
fire to suppress the position of the Ukrainian
огонь на подавление позиции украинских
security forces by numbers  mortar bank were
силовиков на числа ступку берегу были
don't let us eq  oh how the chemist decided
don't let us эколо как химик решил
to assign the 2 quarter to our usual rear
возложить на наш обычный об тыл 2
until you see, that is, it turns out so
до видите то есть получается так
Zakharchenko, it turns out, yes, that is, these
захарченко получается да то есть вот эти
terrorists still fired at
террористы все-таки обстреливали
Mariupol, and
мариуполь так и
it’s not me who came up with it in your
это ведь это не я придумал это в вашем
report, that’s what you read without unnecessary
отчете вот который вы читаете без лишней
everything  still, if there are reports, and without it,
все таки есть если отчеты а без ей
read thoughtfully, then you can get a
читать вдумчиво так то можно получить
very interesting picture, of
очень интересную картину
course, you need to sort of collect and
ну конечно то надо как бы собирать и
end body
торцевая организм
two
два
professionals like you
профессионала как у с тобой
and drive out of your own or smile and how
из свои гнать или улыбаться так и как
beautiful
красиво
but drove you higher, my reports
но загнал вас выше своим отчётам
confirmed my  the words of
подтвердили выйти мои слова
what he finished off that the
чего что он добили что
donbass in the bombing mariupol peaceful
донбасс в бомбее мариуполь мирный
mariupol ukrainian
мариуполя украинские
troops did not say
войска не сказал
survives we just want then from the
выживает только что захотим тогда с
east direction mobile we love the
восточного направления mobile мы любим
graph noted that he gave the order about and the
график отметил что дал приказ об и
dark creature
темная
would have bombed mariupol on the veil and
бы пелена бомбили мариуполь на а
now back to
теперь вернёмся к
who  which country the army of which country
кто какая страна армия какой страны
dropped a bomb an aerial bomb to jump over the
скинула бомбу авиабомбу на прыгать над
drama theater in Mariupol where there were a bunch of
драм театр в мариуполе где была куча
refugees  Russia was hiding, dropped an
беженцев пряталась вот россия сбросила
aerial bomb and there about 600 people
авиабомбу и там около 600 человек
died
погибло
until
до
if this is so, it will be investigated and
если это так то это будет расследовано и
investigated  broke the battle no one then
посмотрите разбила боя никто тогда
remember and also 3 and we can know for sure,
помните и также 3 и можем это точно
put yourself now, based on the
ставьте себе мы сейчас на основании
opinion from the Ukrainian side, we will
мнению с украинской стороны будем
talk about the fact that our troops are
говорить о в том что наши войска
engaged in genocide of the Ukrainian
занимается геноцидом украине украинских
Ukrainian population in Ukraine, well, you yourself
украинского населения ну вы вообще сами
understand this, this is generally possible
понимаете вот это это вообще возможно
no of course that  or the Russians can’t
нет конечно что или не могут русские
engage in genocide of
заниматься геноцидом
course no, no, they have already done it more than once
конечно нет как нет занимает уже не раз
, but why and when and in the
занимались но почему а когда и в
twentieth century they did it until
двадцатом веке занимались до
let’s let’s finish about
давайте давайте давайте закончим про
the bombing of Mariupol
бомбардировку мариуполя я вас должны по
Mariupol with
мариуполь
air bombs Russia bombed the sea with air bombs
авиабомбами россия бомбила авиабомбами
why in 2022 now in
какому в 2022 вот сейчас
February, March and April, and I can suggest
феврале марте и апреле и могу предложить
that if there were Ukrainian
что если там находились украинские
security forces who bombed the
силовики которые бомбили
eastern direction
восточное направление
in response, in response, they could receive the
в ответ в ответ они могли получать
appropriate
соответствующие
corresponding answer, that is, I
соответствующий ответ то есть я
go, that is, it turns out there, not if
хожу то есть получается там не если там
there were exactly
находились там точно находились
Ukrainians there  yen, then without if there are
украинский вы иены то без если там точно
definitely Ukrainian yens there and around Mariupol there
есть украинскими иены и вокруг мариуполя
would definitely be Russian military
бы точно были русские военные российский
Russian and
так и
Russian aviation bombed Mariupol
российская авиация бомбила мариупольский
dropped a bomb on Mariupol so a bomb
скидывала бомба на мариуполь так а бомба
aerial bomb you that on this 500000 reef would be
авиабомба вы что на этом 500000 рифа бы
so this is not selective action
так это не выборочного действия
documents this is not the exact movement that  -it
документах это не точное движение что-то
took aim in the tank but it banged there it
прицелился в танке но бахнуло там она
demolishes a bunch of manpower so peaceful without
сносит кучу живой силы так мирные не
disassembling there you are peaceful or a military man it
разбирая там мирные ты или военный
turns out these are all the dead
получается вот эти все погибшие
civilians in Mariupol so people around
гражданские в мариуполе так люди окато
these Olya bombings so you
этих оля бомбардировок так вот вам
didn’t die this evening Shushanik not for
вечера этого не погибли шушаник не за
shelling
обстрел
but
а
that’s all  for some reason, russian photos from grishka
вот все русские почему-то фото от гришки
are obvious things
это очевидные вещи
no years and
нет лет и
they  not that night they didn’t die from an air bomb
они не ту ночь они нет ни от авиабомбы
, they probably died from your
погибли они наверно погибли от ваших
shooting, it could be
отстрела может быть
air bombs and who in the hall of the drama theater
авиабомб и кто зале драмтеатра
people who
люди которые
hid in the drama theater in a bomb shelter from
прятались драмтеатре в бомбоубежище от
this from shelling, so they threw this
этого от обстрелов так скинули вот эту
powerful bomb so you filled up the drama theater
мощную бомбу так на драмтеатр завалили
under the rubble, all amely almost all died
вы под завалами погибли все амели почти
you are about to try then try
вы вот-вот пробуйте затем пробуйте
trying google July then no one
пробую google июль то никто же не
denies even yours without denying dasha
отрицает даже ваша не отрицая дашу
aviation in mariupol works
авиация в мариуполе работает
so in wikipedia believe no I don’t
так вот в википедии верите нет я не
really well, what’s
особо ну что тут
everywhere and the Ukrainian authorities the
везде и украинских властей
theater served at the box office that ruined the river
театр служил в кассе погубившая реки
roach by 600 or  1300 civilians,
roach на 600 или 1300 гражданских лиц
I already see some kind of sadness in your eyes,
я уже вижу какой-то печаль ваших глазах
well, look together with the Russian,
ну вот смотреть вместе с российской все
we’ll arrange everything different, Russia didn’t like us for
разных устроим россии у нас не любила по
ground targets in the city limits of Mariupol,
наземным целям городской черте мариуполе
and who inflicted on the fact
а кто наносил на то
that, according to the stories of refugees, for a minute,
что по рассказам беженцев на минуту
sprinkled the ends placed on the upper
подсыпал концов разместили на верхних
floors and  rather rotten its points and keep
этажах и а прогнил ее точки и удерживай
civilians in it at the same strong
в нем мирные жители у той же сильно
base hall price mined the building
опорную зал цена заминировали здание
then fill up  Xia
затем заваливаться
who who beat if if not Russia then who
кто кто побил если если не россия то кто
threw off the air bomb
скинул авиабомбу
look who threw off the air bomb novelty I
смотрите кто скинул авиабомбу новинка я
read that the bomber of Russia, that is, that the
читаю что бомбер россии то есть что
sheep blew up how they blew up then the air
взорвали овцы как взорвали то авиабомбы
bombs did
это не
n’t
не
dominate, but then it didn’t blow up or
доминировали да не затем взорвался или
editing the damn thing, I understood in short Russia, you know,
правка блин я понял короче россия знаете
now it’s throwing China  deductible air bombs
вот кидает китай авиабомбы
you read there according to the version
вычета вы читаете там по версии
of some refugees, and therefore the grandmother said
какого-то беженцы а потому бабка сказала
that the grandmother said that so the whole
что бабка сказала что так вот был весь
world was watching, and
мир смотрит а
here,
тут
look, the mission is all the third party
смотри миссия всё третья сторона
said that the Russian military are
заявила что российский военный несут
responsible for marking the mur of the
ответственность за маркировкой мур
Russian theater for war
русского театра за по военным
crimes
преступлениям
bosses that you  wear it
босе которые вы носите
like that, all the same, yes, too, the mission everything
виде так все таки да тоже миссия всё
that you trust says that
который вы доверяете говорит что
after all, the Russians blew up this theater they
все-таки русски взорвали это театр
threw bombs, you need to figure it out,
кинули бомбочки надо надо разобраться да
but when all the lungs I approach a corner
вот когда у всех лёгких я подход в угол
and they drive me to the donat to figure it out, it
и и загоняют на доната разобраться на из
turns out that you are watching which
получается что смотрите какой
display you are  already we already we have already sorted
дисплей вы уже мы уже мы уже разобрали
it out so you told a lie to give and
так что вы говорили неправду дать и
then about the shelling and then of it turns out
потом про обстрелы и тут of оказывается
you read the region to me, it turned out
вы мне зачитывали область ей оказалось
that what you counted was that these were the
что то что вы засчитали что это
physicists of this DPR, your
физики этого днр ваши
pro-Russian ones, they fired at peaceful
пророссийские они обстреливали мирные
seas with air bombs from you,
морю с вас точность
now, too, they said
авиабомбами теперь тоже вот всё сказали
it all, I didn’t invent it for spat, you know,
это не я придумал для плюнул понимаете
civilians in my field they didn’t shell,
мирные моем поле они не обстреливали я
I didn’t talk about it,
об этом не говорил
I  it’s already clear with you from our conversations,
я с вами из нашей разговоры уже понятно
that is, in this they spoke and spoke in a
так то есть в этом говорили и говорили
duet, you will recognize your clear goals,
дуэтом узнаете ваши понятно цели
infect and shadows of doubt, but I’ll
заразите и тени сомнения но я я
point out the shelling of doubt, they don’t, I
обстрелов укажу сомнение есть они не я
agree to trite, so I want to confirm yes,
согласна трите вот я хочу подтвердить да
what I see I am with different characters
что я вижу я с разными персонажами
now  you are not like that there is
сейчас у вас нет такого там
absolutely not everything so you are at
категорически не всё так вы по крайней
least trying to figure it out somewhere, you have to
мере пытаетесь где-то разобраться надо
say you know about this,
сказать знаете вот по поводу этого вот
if you are wrong
если вы не правы
if we are wrong in this situation, then I
если мы не правы данной ситуации то я
think that Russia as such will no
думаю что россию как таковое больше
longer exist, we also think so
существовать не будет мы тоже так думаем
by the way,
кстати
I told you, I, I, I can’t be a high
я вам говорил я я я не могу себя высоком
patriot, but apart from Russia, I don’t need anything from
патриотом но кроме россии мне ничего не
any other country and warm, not
надо никакой другой страны и теплой не
hot, not any  you need to be poor, not
жаркой не никакой не надо небогатой не
poor, I want to tell you that if we are
бедный я вам хочу сказать что если мы не
wrong,
правы
I am more than sure that in a
я более чем уверен то в
stack with this,
стаке с такой
if we are completely wrong with this, but
если мы не правы с такой полностью но
you know that
знаете что вот
most of the population, all my
большая часть населения все мои
relatives, all my friends, when reading,
родственники все мои знакомые читая
I’m sure they don’t see that it’s hopeless
уверен не видят что что это безвыходная
a situation that of course led to
ситуация которая конечно привела к
huge casualties
огромным жертвам
this is a hopeless situation in order to prevent
это безвыходная ситуация чтобы не
even more significant step you can say whatever you want on your
значительных еще больше шаг вы можете
feet yes but the
ногах угодно говорить что угодно да ну а
situation is fine at what an inclination to
ситуация штраф под каким наклоном к
such an
таким
obtuse angle that I appreciate it look it
тупым углом что его ценю смотрите мне
seems to me that here is the situation just
кажется что вот ситуация как раз
showing that 8  in eight years, even
показываю что 8 за восемь лет даже если
if Ukrainians bombed there where
там украинцы бомбили где
there wasn’t even a total for eight years,
не было даже суммарно за восемь лет
as much as even in one
столько же сколько даже в одном
Mariupol, as much as in Kharkov, I
мариуполе так сколько в харьков меня вот
personally know one mathematician in
лично знакомая одна математика на в
Kharkov, died from shelling, so but you’re
харькове погибла от обстрела так но вам
not here, it’s good that you want to
не сюда это хорошо что вы хотите
figure it out  you don’t have such a thing, you know cheers
разобраться у вас нет такого знаете ура
for 32 there, in the Crimea, we’ll capture its main
по 32 там у крым его основным захватим
volume, as some say, but here you are
объеме как некоторые говорят а вот вы по
at least  you are trying to figure it out very
крайней мере пытаетесь разобраться очень
well that you are watching the same reports on
хорошо что вы смотрите те же отчеты о б
the OBS but how would you understand the
с е так но как бы их чтобы понять вот
game here you would come to Ukraine and
игру вот вы бы приехали в украину так и
talk with people who here
пообщались с людьми которые тут очень
left Donetsk a lot from Mariupol from
много уехал из донецка с мариуполь от
these militants here  why Donetsk
вот этих боевиков то тут почему донецк
is under occupation and not developed and
под оккупацией стоит и не развивать и
people don’t want to go there, their people leave,
люди не хотят туда их люди уезжают он
having won Kharkov, and I
снискав харьков так а у меня знакомый
know just Donetsk
как раз донецке
vectors of 1 branch of the university in Russia
векторы 1 филиала университета в россии
from Donetsk,
из донецка
beautiful and Russian
прекрасных и русского
flourish here, okay, look well,
процветают сюда окей хорошо смотреть
thank you for the conversation, so that is
спасибо вам за разговор так то есть
we got an interesting one, we
интересный у нас получился нам очень
would really like to teach our topic
хотелось бы нашу вот эту тему учили
here, especially Mariupol, so that we,
особенно вот мариуполь так ему чтоб нам
as it were, I see that the Russians will tell
как бы вот я вижу что русские расскажу
us that we bombed it, we love it because
что это мы бомбили мы любим потому что
there were hiding as if the military had
там прятались как бы военные надо было
to go out of town in an open field
им выйти за город в чисто поле тебе
all the military men come down to you and they blame the
снижаются все все военные они и обвиняют
cities and it has always been like this, that is, with the
города и так было так всегда так то есть
right moment the microphone is stretched
правом миг микрофон микрофон тянутся
well, it’s hard to hear
ну плохо слышно но чем жертвует
read it, yes, I’ll also read it for my part and we’ll see in a month or two how it pops up, and yet you said a very interesting version of the ladies that if it turns out that it was all such a spoon from Russia, it will no longer exist, it seems to me a lot Russian Russians, then in a month or two they will already look at it all not even like they looked two months ago that we will capture Kyiv there in three days, and if you are right, and if you are wires, then we have a lot of people to think and many Christmas trees and sticks indeed, such a nation of fascists is a birth gang, it will not be the same, we understand what will happen, and if the other is not wrong, you will change your point of view, most likely because well, what else remains for them, yes, you have already lost a lot, but most likely if you are wrong, as such, the country of Ukraine, it will cease to exist quite quickly, you know, with our national, it turns out that there is a confrontation between the collapse of 2 states of ours more in our guinea st islan  d bay in ours
нашем гиней ст island bay в нашем
in our anthem there are such words to look
в нашем гимне есть такие слова взглянуть
at what a red-haired color in the sun what
на чего рыженький окраса на солнце что
is our enemies wearing and trembling kid
же носящего наши наши враги и дрожим kid
ink and not dead they will disappear and perish like
ink а не погиб пропадут и сгинут как
dew in the sun so now I look
роса на солнце так и вот сейчас я смотрю
out the window just the solar
в окно начинается как раз солнечный
period begins  so May is summer and so it
период так май лето так и вот мне
seems to me that this will be the
кажется что это будет
time of the victory of ukraine
временем победы украины
glory to ukraine then
слава украине то
all this thanks and didn’t
все это спасибо да не
overwork such tick characters until almost along the
вот такие тиковые персонаж до почти по
paths of alvin feature we are trying out of this I will
тропам алвин фича пробуем из этом я вам
now show you Vasily already once I will show without
сейчас покажу василия уже раз покажу без
I will even say everything and  here, of course, in the
я даже скажу всё и тут конечно вот в
15th year there, such as the shelling of Mariupol,
15-м году там типа обстрела мариуполя
Ukraine, Lapin, so many that working from the
украины лапина столькими что работа с
eastern direction, these are the
восточное направление это те и
ones that almost always extinguished us, the truth is,
затушила всегда почти нас правде
Russian propaganda just
российская пропаганда просто по
piled on them and sticks of any line a book
наваливал а им стики всякого line a book
and so in it the real world of this you and
так и вот в ней реальном мире этого ты и
pay their casing that they say they are dependent on rocky,
плати кожуха их что мол на зависим рокив
so there Ukraine was ours,
так там украина была наша ну и
and the acoustics were a victim in that conflict, I’m
и акустики жертвой в том конфликте на я
such a bast, I howled there for two months in
таковы лыка я туда два месяца завыли в
Mariupol far cry
мариуполе far cry так
and up to  here these people wake up to the point,
и до сюда этих людей просыпается толку
but to start, but because there they boasted
но начинать а потому что там хвались
like equis there, the Azov people drink bottled water from water,
типа equis там азовцев от воды пить
it’s not afraid, and the kist March
бутылкам это нет не боится и киста март
shelling was
обстрелы были
in the Donbass that
на донбассе that атомными пик бутылками
there were so many atomic peak bottles here it turns out, but here
так было много тут то получается а тут
networks and God are also azos there  access
сетях и бога тоже азос там по доступу
to the hatch itself, the love of the grooves and then it was 8
самому люку любовь пазов и затем было 8
rubles, so
руб так так
winsxs the same garno phrase came to me if we turn out to be false,
winsxs же дуже гарно фразу мне у нас
then
подалась если мы окажемся неправда то
Russia will no longer be so there is already a
россии больше не будет так воны уже дуже
lot of mana data, there are guys,
багато данных маны почин там парни все
we’ll all take cues in three days, but at a time for  once
возьмем киев за три дня а за раз за раз
the doses of the ticking processes in Russia begin,
начинается дозы тикали процессы в россии
so let the processes of the collapse of the Russian one
так пусть и процессы распада российской
held on, we kept them at a time, Kit
держалась мы их за раз ботинки кит
Kisarov’s boots, so and then minutes before such
кисарова так а потом минуты до таким
an avalanche of the underground and
знать и снеговые ком лавину подземной и
we want to get the
мы желаем в достать приемли из 1000 час
cob of the disintegration of the Russian Federation from 1000 hours an hour and
початку распаду российской федерации и
our task  will be the catalyst for this
наша задача будет катализатором этого
process  Itory and
бит широкую аудиторию и
stupid TPP was looking for glory to Ukraine
глупо тэц искал слава украине